{
  "translations": {
    "en": {
      "q2": {
        "type": "true/false",
        "description": "Now we want to show that NPDA’s and CFG both represent CFL’s. Show that we can take any CFG and construct a NPDA and vice versa.",
        "question": "CFL stands for Context-Free Languages",
        "answer": "True",
        "choices": []
      },
      "q3": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Now we want to show that NPDA’s and CFG both represent CFL’s. Show that we can take any CFG and construct a NPDA and vice versa.",
        "question": "What is context free language?",
        "answer": "a languages that has a context free grammar",
        "choices": ["a languages that has a context free grammar", "a language that has a regular expression", "set of strings"]
      },
      "q4": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Now we want to show that NPDA’s and CFG both represent CFL’s. Show that we can take any CFG and construct a NPDA and vice versa.",
        "question": "What is CFG?",
        "answer": "CFG is a grammar that has only one variable in the LHS of each production",
        "choices": ["CFG is a grammar that has only one variable in the LHS of each production", "CFG is a grammar that has at most one variable on the RHS of each production", "a grammar that has no restrictions on both LHS and RHS of each production"]
      },
      "q5": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Now we want to show that NPDA’s and CFG both represent CFL’s. Show that we can take any CFG and construct a NPDA and vice versa.",
        "question": "What is NPDA?",
        "answer": "Non-deterministic Pushdown Automata",
        "choices": ["Non-deterministic Pushdown Automata", "Deterministic Pushdown Automata"]
      },
      "q6": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Now we want to show that NPDA’s and CFG both represent CFL’s. Show that we can take any CFG and construct a NPDA and vice versa.",
        "question": "What are PDA components?",
        "answer": ["$Q$ for states", "$\\Sigma$ for the alphabets", "$\\Gamma$ for the stack alphabets", "$\\delta$ for the transition function", "$q_0$ for the start state", "$z$ for the stack start symbol", "$F$ for set of final states"],
        "choices": ["$Q$ for states", "$\\Sigma$ for the alphabets", "$\\Gamma$ for the stack alphabets", "$\\delta$ for the transition function", "$q_0$ for the start state", "$z$ for the stack start symbol", "$F$ for set of final states"]
      },
      "q9": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Theorem: For any CFL $L$ not containing $\\lambda$, $\\exists$ a NPDA $M$ such that $L=L(M)$.<br/>To prove that we need to find a method to sketch the NPDA form a CFG.<br/>Given ($\\lambda$ free) CFL $L$.",
        "question": "Since $L$ is a CFL, then there must be ... for it",
        "answer": "CFG",
        "choices": ["CFG", "NFA", "PDA"]
      },
      "q10": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Theorem: For any CFL $L$ not containing $\\lambda$, $\\exists$ a NPDA $M$ such that $L=L(M)$.<br/>To prove that we need to find a method to sketch the NPDA form a CFG.<br/>Given ($\\lambda$ free) CFL $L$, $\\exists$ CFG $G$ such that $L=L(G)$.<br/>$\\exists$ $G\\prime$ in GNF, such that $L(G) = L(G\\prime)$",
        "question": "GNF means",
        "answer": "Greibach Normal Form",
        "choices": ["Greibach Normal Form", "Chomskey Normal Form"]
      },
      "q11": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Theorem: For any CFL $L$ not containing $\\lambda$, $\\exists$ a NPDA $M$ such that $L=L(M)$.<br/>To prove that we need to find a method to sketch the NPDA form a CFG.<br/>Given ($\\lambda$ free) CFL $L$, $\\exists$ CFG $G$ such that $L=L(G)$.<br/>$\\exists$ $G\\prime$ in GNF, such that $L(G) = L(G\\prime)$",
        "question": "If a grammar $G' = (V,T,S,P)$ is in GNF, then all productions are in the form",
        "answer": "$A \\rightarrow ax$ where $A \\in V$, $a \\in T$, $x \\in V^*$",
        "choices": ["$A \\rightarrow BC \\quad A \\rightarrow c$, where $A,B,C \\in V$, and $c \\in T$", "$A \\rightarrow B$ where $A,B \\in V$", "$A \\rightarrow \\lambda$ where $A\\in V$", "$A \\rightarrow ax$ where $A \\in V$, $a \\in T$, $x \\in V^*$"]
      },
      "q13": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Theorem: For any CFL $L$ not containing $\\lambda$, $\\exists$ a NPDA $M$ such that $L=L(M)$.<br/>To prove that we need to find a method to sketch the NPDA form a CFG.<br/>Given ($\\lambda$ free) CFL $L$, $\\exists$ CFG $G$ such that $L=L(G)$.<br/>$\\exists$ $G\\prime$ in GNF, such that $L(G) = L(G\\prime)$<br/>We need to construct NPDA $M = (Q, \\Sigma, \\Gamma, \\delta, q_0, z, F)$, where $Q = \\{q_0, q_1, q_f\\}, \\Sigma = T, \\Gamma = V \\cup \\{z\\}, F = \\{q_f\\}$",
        "question": "Consider the CFG on the left, we need to convert it to a PDA. How many states we need for the PDA?",
        "answer": "3",
        "choices": ["2","3","4","5"]
      },
      "q14": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Theorem: For any CFL $L$ not containing $\\lambda$, $\\exists$ a NPDA $M$ such that $L=L(M)$.<br/>To prove that we need to find a method to sketch the NPDA form a CFG.<br/>Given ($\\lambda$ free) CFL $L$, $\\exists$ CFG $G$ such that $L=L(G)$.<br/>$\\exists$ $G\\prime$ in GNF, such that $L(G) = L(G\\prime)$<br/>We need to construct NPDA $M = (Q, \\Sigma, \\Gamma, \\delta, q_0, z, F)$, where $Q = \\{q_0, q_1, q_f\\}, \\Sigma = T, \\Gamma = V \\cup \\{z\\}, F = \\{q_f\\}$",
        "question": "Which state is the start state?",
        "answer": "$q_0$",
        "choices": ["$q_0$", "$q_1$", "$q_f$"]
      },
      "q15": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Theorem: For any CFL $L$ not containing $\\lambda$, $\\exists$ a NPDA $M$ such that $L=L(M)$.<br/>To prove that we need to find a method to sketch the NPDA form a CFG.<br/>Given ($\\lambda$ free) CFL $L$, $\\exists$ CFG $G$ such that $L=L(G)$.<br/>$\\exists$ $G\\prime$ in GNF, such that $L(G) = L(G\\prime)$<br/>We need to construct NPDA $M = (Q, \\Sigma, \\Gamma, \\delta, q_0, z, F)$, where $Q = \\{q_0, q_1, q_f\\}, \\Sigma = T, \\Gamma = V \\cup \\{z\\}, F = \\{q_f\\}$",
        "question": "Which state is the final state?",
        "answer": "$q_f$",
        "choices": ["$q_0$", "$q_1$", "$q_f$"]
      },
      "q16": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Theorem: For any CFL $L$ not containing $\\lambda$, $\\exists$ a NPDA $M$ such that $L=L(M)$.<br/>To prove that we need to find a method to sketch the NPDA form a CFG.<br/>Given ($\\lambda$ free) CFL $L$, $\\exists$ CFG $G$ such that $L=L(G)$.<br/>$\\exists$ $G\\prime$ in GNF, such that $L(G) = L(G\\prime)$<br/>We need to construct NPDA $M = (Q, \\Sigma, \\Gamma, \\delta, q_0, z, F)$, where $Q = \\{q_0, q_1, q_f\\}, \\Sigma = T, \\Gamma = V \\cup \\{z\\}, F = \\{q_f\\}$",
        "question": "What are the alphabet set for the PDA?",
        "answer": "The Grammar terminals",
        "choices": ["The Grammar terminals", "The Grammar variables", "The Grammar start variable"]
      },
      "q17": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Theorem: For any CFL $L$ not containing $\\lambda$, $\\exists$ a NPDA $M$ such that $L=L(M)$.<br/>To prove that we need to find a method to sketch the NPDA form a CFG.<br/>Given ($\\lambda$ free) CFL $L$, $\\exists$ CFG $G$ such that $L=L(G)$.<br/>$\\exists$ $G\\prime$ in GNF, such that $L(G) = L(G\\prime)$<br/>We need to construct NPDA $M = (Q, \\Sigma, \\Gamma, \\delta, q_0, z, F)$, where $Q = \\{q_0, q_1, q_f\\}, \\Sigma = T, \\Gamma = V \\cup \\{z\\}, F = \\{q_f\\}$",
        "question": "What are the stack alphabet set for the PDA?",
        "answer": ["The Grammar variables","the stack start symbol $z$"],
        "choices": ["The Grammar terminals", "The Grammar variables", "The Grammar start variable", "the stack start symbol $z$"]
      },
      "q18": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Theorem: For any CFL $L$ not containing $\\lambda$, $\\exists$ a NPDA $M$ such that $L=L(M)$.<br/>To prove that we need to find a method to sketch the NPDA form a CFG.<br/>Given ($\\lambda$ free) CFL $L$, $\\exists$ CFG $G$ such that $L=L(G)$.<br/>$\\exists$ $G\\prime$ in GNF, such that $L(G) = L(G\\prime)$<br/>We need to construct NPDA $M = (Q, \\Sigma, \\Gamma, \\delta, q_0, z, F)$, where $Q = \\{q_0, q_1, q_f\\}, \\Sigma = T, \\Gamma = V \\cup \\{z\\}, F = \\{q_f\\}$<br/>1. $M$ starts by putting $S$ on the stack",
        "question": "What is the transition from $q_0$ to $q_1$?",
        "answer": "$\\delta(q_0, \\lambda, z) = (q_1, z)$",
        "choices": ["$\\delta(q_0, \\lambda, z) = (q_1, z)$", "$\\delta(q_0, a, $z$) = (q_1, Sz)$", "$\\delta(q_0, S, $z$) = (q_1, Sz)$"]
      },
      "q19": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Theorem: For any CFL $L$ not containing $\\lambda$, $\\exists$ a NPDA $M$ such that $L=L(M)$.<br/>To prove that we need to find a method to sketch the NPDA form a CFG.<br/>Given ($\\lambda$ free) CFL $L$, $\\exists$ CFG $G$ such that $L=L(G)$.<br/>$\\exists$ $G\\prime$ in GNF, such that $L(G) = L(G\\prime)$<br/>We need to construct NPDA $M = (Q, \\Sigma, \\Gamma, \\delta, q_0, z, F)$, where $Q = \\{q_0, q_1, q_f\\}, \\Sigma = T, \\Gamma = V \\cup \\{z\\}, F = \\{q_f\\}$<br/>1. $M$ starts by putting $S$ on the stack<br/>2. For each production $A \\rightarrow a X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n$ put $(q_1, X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n)$ in $\\delta(q_1, a, A)$<br/>In other words: (Pop A from the stack, read “a” from tape, and push $X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n$ onto the stack)",
        "question": "What is the transition for the highlighted production?",
        "answer": "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, SA)$",
        "choices": ["$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, SA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, $S$) = (q_1, SSA)$"]
      },
      "q20": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Theorem: For any CFL $L$ not containing $\\lambda$, $\\exists$ a NPDA $M$ such that $L=L(M)$.<br/>To prove that we need to find a method to sketch the NPDA form a CFG.<br/>Given ($\\lambda$ free) CFL $L$, $\\exists$ CFG $G$ such that $L=L(G)$.<br/>$\\exists$ $G\\prime$ in GNF, such that $L(G) = L(G\\prime)$<br/>We need to construct NPDA $M = (Q, \\Sigma, \\Gamma, \\delta, q_0, z, F)$, where $Q = \\{q_0, q_1, q_f\\}, \\Sigma = T, \\Gamma = V \\cup \\{z\\}, F = \\{q_f\\}$<br/>1. $M$ starts by putting $S$ on the stack<br/>2. For each production $A \\rightarrow a X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n$ put $(q_1, X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n)$ in $\\delta(q_1, a, A)$<br/>In other words: (Pop A from the stack, read “a” from tape, and push $X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n$ onto the stack)",
        "question": "What is the transition for the highlighted production?",
        "answer": "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, AA)$",
        "choices": ["$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, AA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, AAS)$"]
      },
      "q21": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Theorem: For any CFL $L$ not containing $\\lambda$, $\\exists$ a NPDA $M$ such that $L=L(M)$.<br/>To prove that we need to find a method to sketch the NPDA form a CFG.<br/>Given ($\\lambda$ free) CFL $L$, $\\exists$ CFG $G$ such that $L=L(G)$.<br/>$\\exists$ $G\\prime$ in GNF, such that $L(G) = L(G\\prime)$<br/>We need to construct NPDA $M = (Q, \\Sigma, \\Gamma, \\delta, q_0, z, F)$, where $Q = \\{q_0, q_1, q_f\\}, \\Sigma = T, \\Gamma = V \\cup \\{z\\}, F = \\{q_f\\}$<br/>1. $M$ starts by putting $S$ on the stack<br/>2. For each production $A \\rightarrow a X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n$ put $(q_1, X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n)$ in $\\delta(q_1, a, A)$<br/>In other words: (Pop A from the stack, read “a” from tape, and push $X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n$ onto the stack)",
        "question": "What is the transition for the highlighted production?",
        "answer": "$\\delta(q_1, b, S) = (q_1, \\lambda)$",
        "choices": ["$\\delta(q_1, b, S) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, S) = (q_1, S)$"]
      },
      "q22": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Theorem: For any CFL $L$ not containing $\\lambda$, $\\exists$ a NPDA $M$ such that $L=L(M)$.<br/>To prove that we need to find a method to sketch the NPDA form a CFG.<br/>Given ($\\lambda$ free) CFL $L$, $\\exists$ CFG $G$ such that $L=L(G)$.<br/>$\\exists$ $G\\prime$ in GNF, such that $L(G) = L(G\\prime)$<br/>We need to construct NPDA $M = (Q, \\Sigma, \\Gamma, \\delta, q_0, z, F)$, where $Q = \\{q_0, q_1, q_f\\}, \\Sigma = T, \\Gamma = V \\cup \\{z\\}, F = \\{q_f\\}$<br/>1. $M$ starts by putting $S$ on the stack<br/>2. For each production $A \\rightarrow a X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n$ put $(q_1, X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n)$ in $\\delta(q_1, a, A)$<br/>In other words: (Pop A from the stack, read “a” from tape, and push $X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n$ onto the stack)",
        "question": "What is the transition for the highlighted production?",
        "answer": "$\\delta(q_1, b, A) = (q_1, BBB)$",
        "choices": ["$\\delta(q_1, b, A) = (q_1, BBB)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, S) = (q_1, BBB)$"]
      },
      "q23": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Theorem: For any CFL $L$ not containing $\\lambda$, $\\exists$ a NPDA $M$ such that $L=L(M)$.<br/>To prove that we need to find a method to sketch the NPDA form a CFG.<br/>Given ($\\lambda$ free) CFL $L$, $\\exists$ CFG $G$ such that $L=L(G)$.<br/>$\\exists$ $G\\prime$ in GNF, such that $L(G) = L(G\\prime)$<br/>We need to construct NPDA $M = (Q, \\Sigma, \\Gamma, \\delta, q_0, z, F)$, where $Q = \\{q_0, q_1, q_f\\}, \\Sigma = T, \\Gamma = V \\cup \\{z\\}, F = \\{q_f\\}$<br/>1. $M$ starts by putting $S$ on the stack<br/>2. For each production $A \\rightarrow a X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n$ put $(q_1, X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n)$ in $\\delta(q_1, a, A)$<br/>In other words: (Pop A from the stack, read “a” from tape, and push $X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n$ onto the stack)",
        "question": "What is the transition for the highlighted production?",
        "answer": "$\\delta(q_1, b, B) = (q_1, \\lambda)$",
        "choices": ["$\\delta(q_1, b, B) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, $B$) = (q_1, B)$"]
      },
      "q24": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Theorem: For any CFL $L$ not containing $\\lambda$, $\\exists$ a NPDA $M$ such that $L=L(M)$.<br/>To prove that we need to find a method to sketch the NPDA form a CFG.<br/>Given ($\\lambda$ free) CFL $L$, $\\exists$ CFG $G$ such that $L=L(G)$.<br/>$\\exists$ $G\\prime$ in GNF, such that $L(G) = L(G\\prime)$<br/>We need to construct NPDA $M = (Q, \\Sigma, \\Gamma, \\delta, q_0, z, F)$, where $Q = \\{q_0, q_1, q_f\\}, \\Sigma = T, \\Gamma = V \\cup \\{z\\}, F = \\{q_f\\}$<br/>1. $M$ starts by putting $S$ on the stack<br/>2. For each production $A \\rightarrow a X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n$ put $(q_1, X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n)$ in $\\delta(q_1, a, A)$<br/>In other words: (Pop A from the stack, read “a” from tape, and push $X_1 X_2 \\ldots X_n$ onto the stack)<br/>3. Accept if $S \\stackrel{*}{\\Rightarrow} w \\in \\Sigma^*$ (all variables on the stack are replaced by terminals or λ)",
        "question": "Once we reach $z$ means that all variables are converted to terminals or $\\lambda$ and poped form the stack. What is the transition from $q_1$ to $q_f$?",
        "answer": "$\\delta(q_1, \\lambda, z) = (q_f, z)$",
        "choices": ["$\\delta(q_1, \\lambda, z) = (q_f, z)$", "$\\delta(q_1, \\lambda, S) = (q_f, S)$"]
      },
      "q27": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Trace $abbbbb$ in the grammar and in the PDA. Let us start by trace that the string is in the grammar.",
        "question": "Starting from $S$, what is the production we need to use to derive $abbbbb$",
        "answer": "1",
        "choices": ["1","2", "3", "4","5"]
      },
      "q28": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Trace $abbbbb$ in the grammar and in the PDA. Let us start by trace that the string is in the grammar.",
        "question": "Now we have $S \\Rightarrow aSA$, what is the next production we need to use to derive $\\textbf{a}bbbbb$",
        "answer": "3",
        "choices": ["1","2", "3", "4","5"]
      },
      "q29": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Trace $abbbbb$ in the grammar and in the PDA. Let us start by trace that the string is in the grammar.",
        "question": "Now we have $S \\Rightarrow aSA \\Rightarrow abA$, what is the next production we need to use to derive $\\textbf{ab}bbbb$",
        "answer": "4",
        "choices": ["1","2", "3", "4","5"]
      },
      "q30": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Trace $abbbbb$ in the grammar and in the PDA. Let us start by trace that the string is in the grammar.",
        "question": "Now we have $S \\Rightarrow aSA \\Rightarrow abA\\Rightarrow abbBBB$, what is the next production we need to use to derive $\\textbf{abb}bbb$",
        "answer": "5",
        "choices": ["1","2", "3", "4","5"]
      },
      "q31": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Trace $abbbbb$ in the grammar and in the PDA. Let us start by trace that the string is in the grammar.",
        "question": "Now we have $S \\Rightarrow aSA \\Rightarrow abA\\Rightarrow abbBBB \\Rightarrow abbbBB$, what is the next production we need to use to derive $\\textbf{abbb}bb$",
        "answer": "5",
        "choices": ["1","2", "3", "4","5"]
      },
      "q32": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Trace $abbbbb$ in the grammar and in the PDA. Let us start by trace that the string is in the grammar.",
        "question": "Now we have $S \\Rightarrow aSA \\Rightarrow abA\\Rightarrow abbBBB \\Rightarrow abbbBB$, what is the next production we need to use to derive $\\textbf{abbb}bb$",
        "answer": "5",
        "choices": ["1","2", "3", "4","5"]
      },
      "q33": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Trace $abbbbb$ in the grammar and in the PDA. Let us start by trace that the string is in the grammar.",
        "question": "Now we have $S \\Rightarrow aSA \\Rightarrow abA\\Rightarrow abbBBB \\Rightarrow abbbBB \\Rightarrow abbbbB$, what is the next production we need to use to derive $\\textbf{abbbb}b$",
        "answer": "5",
        "choices": ["1","2", "3", "4","5"]
      },
      "q34": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Now we have $S \\Rightarrow aSA \\Rightarrow abA\\Rightarrow abbBBB \\Rightarrow abbbBB \\Rightarrow abbbbB \\Rightarrow abbbbb$. The sring is derived form the grammar.",
        "question": "Let us do the same in the PDA, what is the transition we should start with?",
        "answer": "$\\delta(q_0, \\lambda, z) = (q_1, Sz)$",
        "choices": ["$\\delta(q_0, \\lambda, z) = (q_1, Sz)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, SA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, AA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, S) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, A) = (q_1, BBB)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, B) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, \\lambda, z) = (q_f, z)$"]
      },
      "q35": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Now we have $S \\Rightarrow aSA \\Rightarrow abA\\Rightarrow abbBBB \\Rightarrow abbbBB \\Rightarrow abbbbB \\Rightarrow abbbbb$. The sring is derived form the grammar.",
        "question": "What is the next transition?",
        "answer": "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, SA)$",
        "choices": ["$\\delta(q_0, \\lambda, z) = (q_1, z)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, SA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, AA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, S) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, A) = (q_1, BBB)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, B) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, \\lambda, z) = (q_f, z)$"]
      },
      "q36": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Now we have $S \\Rightarrow aSA \\Rightarrow abA\\Rightarrow abbBBB \\Rightarrow abbbBB \\Rightarrow abbbbB \\Rightarrow abbbbb$. The sring is derived form the grammar.",
        "question": "What is the next transition?",
        "answer": "$\\delta(q_1, b, S) = (q_1, \\lambda)$",
        "choices": ["$\\delta(q_0, \\lambda, z) = (q_1, z)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, SA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, AA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, S) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, A) = (q_1, BBB)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, B) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, \\lambda, z) = (q_f, z)$"]
      },
      "q37": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Now we have $S \\Rightarrow aSA \\Rightarrow abA\\Rightarrow abbBBB \\Rightarrow abbbBB \\Rightarrow abbbbB \\Rightarrow abbbbb$. The sring is derived form the grammar.",
        "question": "What is the next transition?",
        "answer": "$\\delta(q_1, b, A) = (q_1, BBB)$",
        "choices": ["$\\delta(q_0, \\lambda, z) = (q_1, z)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, SA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, AA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, S) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, A) = (q_1, BBB)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, B) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, \\lambda, z) = (q_f, z)$"]
      },
      "q38": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Now we have $S \\Rightarrow aSA \\Rightarrow abA\\Rightarrow abbBBB \\Rightarrow abbbBB \\Rightarrow abbbbB \\Rightarrow abbbbb$. The sring is derived form the grammar.",
        "question": "What is the next transition?",
        "answer": "$\\delta(q_1, b, B) = (q_1, \\lambda)$",
        "choices": ["$\\delta(q_0, \\lambda, z) = (q_1, z)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, SA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, AA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, S) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, A) = (q_1, BBB)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, B) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, \\lambda, z) = (q_f, z)$"]
      },
      "q39": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Now we have $S \\Rightarrow aSA \\Rightarrow abA\\Rightarrow abbBBB \\Rightarrow abbbBB \\Rightarrow abbbbB \\Rightarrow abbbbb$. The sring is derived form the grammar.",
        "question": "What is the next transition?",
        "answer": "$\\delta(q_1, b, B) = (q_1, \\lambda)$",
        "choices": ["$\\delta(q_0, \\lambda, z) = (q_1, z)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, SA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, AA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, S) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, A) = (q_1, BBB)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, B) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, \\lambda, z) = (q_f, z)$"]
      },
      "q40": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Now we have $S \\Rightarrow aSA \\Rightarrow abA\\Rightarrow abbBBB \\Rightarrow abbbBB \\Rightarrow abbbbB \\Rightarrow abbbbb$. The sring is derived form the grammar.",
        "question": "What is the next transition?",
        "answer": "$\\delta(q_1, b, B) = (q_1, \\lambda)$",
        "choices": ["$\\delta(q_0, \\lambda, z) = (q_1, z)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, SA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, AA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, S) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, A) = (q_1, BBB)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, B) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, \\lambda, z) = (q_f, z)$"]
      },
      "q41": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Now we have $S \\Rightarrow aSA \\Rightarrow abA\\Rightarrow abbBBB \\Rightarrow abbbBB \\Rightarrow abbbbB \\Rightarrow abbbbb$. The sring is derived form the grammar.",
        "question": "What is the next transition?",
        "answer": "$\\delta(q_1, \\lambda, z) = (q_f, z)$",
        "choices": ["$\\delta(q_0, \\lambda, z) = (q_1, z)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, SA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, a, S) = (q_1, AA)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, S) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, A) = (q_1, BBB)$", "$\\delta(q_1, b, B) = (q_1, \\lambda)$", "$\\delta(q_1, \\lambda, z) = (q_f, z)$"]
      }
    }
  }
}